In 2020, 25, when the invocation of the past was passed, we passed the first research, and then I'll leave the truth.
Father, thank you that you're listening, and that we can talk to you, and you care about what we do in our homes,
but you also care about what happens here in this room.
Lord, I ask you to bless many workers that are gathered here, help them in those moments when they're tired, frustrated, give them peace,
help the ones that are seated in front of us that have this responsibility.
Give them wisdom, give them courage when they have to make tough decisions.
Father, overall, we ask you to continue to bless our town, and bless ones who give them given gifts so that we might have it.
Do bless this meeting, Lord.
Jesus name my prayer, amen.
Let's lead you to the five of the United States of America, and then to do it about looking for which it stands, one nation, under God, individual, would believe in this as a role.
For, I'm both publicly employed for unscheduled personal parents, five claims live.
How's your proof?
I guess.
Hi.
Hello.
Six minutes in the April 15th, 2020, May 1st, 2020, May 1st, 2020, May 9th, 2020, May 9th, 2020.
Special meeting.
Motion to approve.
Second.
Double.
Hi.
Geoff.
Bales.
Avec.
7 budget.
Dungeon Management.
Over 25, that is 26 baby funds.
One thousand dollars from the $20 Umasmf run to the five, Mike.
So the budget is a solution requires that any money that moves from funds to fund.
from fund to fund be approved by the Council. So that's what we're doing. The merit money was budgeted in fund to 5TN, which is the MSUA fund.
This is the stormwater fund, which is 511, has personnel and this is for the merit race for that.
Thank you.
Yes, so in front of everybody is the resolution and the also the ordinance for the race
We know we've had the we've been talking about this. I think for about a year
You know GRDA is increasing our rates. We're going to do for the next three years
And we had Dan Jackson come down a present then we did the town hall and Dan tonight is actually voting on it
So we'll vote on it tonight on the MSUA and also on the city council so it'll be an ordinance on the city council
So it's for the next three years on a GRDA is talked about
Raising for the next four. They just approved the next three tonight. We're just approving one, though, right?
Well, we
Free three years. It's really we said effort three years is because that's what Dan presented since you know GRDA was doing it for three years, but
So this is on your bill, you know, so we have a PPA charge
This is what GRDA passes on us. We pass on to the customers
So we're actually going to make this easier to calculate. We used to do it. I mean, Derek and it talked a little bit more it's kind of difficult to understand
Yeah, this is kind of cleans it up. It just takes their right at times 1.1 and the Maya's the two cents, which is already built into the
actual right
So the hope is it kind of keeps our PPA PPA that we charged customers a little flatter so that it doesn't
Change as much so it was actually a dance presentation, but
It just fell off
Yeah, that's correct. Yeah, it just rolled off. We got to email this week. I was actually going to do it in my city manager's communication, but
Much to approve
So the strap of the story, your related sign authority, the trusted manor, or is that you mean different?
Good evening.
Good. You'll see in your packets there is a list of MSUA equipment or fleet that we are looking to surplus.
We're trying to get some clean up and get some of this over equipment moved.
My understanding is that the this equipment has gone to our shop and been looked at to see if it's to be used in a different department.
The department also discussions with other departments before we decided to move it here.
So it's been looked at seeing if there's any more useful life in it for the MSUA.
And this is where we're at.
We'd like to do a live auction with these items that are in your packet.
And you'll see similar except different items from the city side.
So once we have approval to move forward with an auction, then we'll I know that my staff's been working with getting some auctioneers looking with others.
I believe on getting, you know, is that we can do that for the public auction?
I know the community always liked it when we did the public auction.
I mean there's a lot of people on the community that come here and buy a whole different things.
You know from computers to equipment to whatever.
Potion to approve.
Second.
Hi.
The list of MSUA electronic equipment including the fact included in the packet.
That's our bus.
And otherwise I've got some versatility auction.
Photographers.
Throwing.
You're left sign authority.
The press manager.
Are there anything.
Yes.
These items.
They had called me to see about moving them out.
Get some more space.
And it's a lot of electronic equipment.
There's a list on the back here.
Some of the things work.
Some don't.
This is some things that we really can't use anymore.
It's possible that some local communities might be able to use some of this.
But the conditions we have some things that work.
There's a few things that we don't know of.
But what we're requesting is to be able to either sell it, scrap it or destroy it.
And we need your approval to move forward.
Motion to approve.
Hi.
12.
Award-beard for Agree.
Rocks-Blice.
2025.
to APEC, Central, Incorporated Campstone, and Policy Construction from this year, 2526, as recommended by staff.
Group contract, continue to pause the mission of all required contract documents.
We received annual pricing from the three rocket rock suppliers you just mentioned through competitive bidding.
The annual rates are for specified rock categories.
Rock purchases will go to the lowest bidder first.
What this does is it helps the save time not to put it out for bid every time something comes up when we need aggregate.
But they'll go to the lowest bidder first, it cascades.
If that company didn't have time to do it, it would cascade to the next one in the pricing.
And we think that this process will help to stay as cost effective and efficient in getting the work complex for the city as we can do.
So what we need is your approval.
Also, there's going to be three, one year extensions, this will be the first extension for an aggregate.
The pricing will stay the same for the extensions.
The extensions will on all of these, yes.
Make a motion we approve.
Second.
All right.
13 awarding on call concrete, repairs C25, dash 10, constant instruction, goings, and enterprise and corporate or stage instruction.
Services, LLC, stock instruction, and tors as construction.
For fiscal year, 2526, as recommended by staff, and approved contract, contingent.
Fund submission of all required contracts.
These are still very similar.
They go in the same process, from lowest to highest.
And all of these companies we've used often on, except for maybe the last one there, but they've done some good work in the city.
We feel like it's a good group.
But we need your approval to approve all of these companies.
So it will happen in our fingertips when we need a motion to approve.
Hi.
14 awarding.
Oh, as they become concrete, sand supplies.
C25, dash 11.
And scoby sand for those of you who are 25, 20, 20, say.
As a revenue by staff, approved contract, contingent, bond, all submission of all required contract documents.
On this.
particular bid, we only received one from the Scotty Sand, and we need your approval for this
one as well.
This one line of construction will be new to submitting.
We've only had my concrete, I'd probably be last couple of times that I've been involved.
They were the only ones we'll have to go to now.
And there's a few variations on different types of concrete.
One might be a little higher than the other on some and vice versa.
But we need your approval to make these available to us as well.
Hi.
And I know contract rules, amendments for Christmas year 2526 is recommended by staff to put
the contracts contingent upon the submission of all of our contract documents for items A to H.
On all of these amendments, we had most of the companies that we've been dealing with, go ahead and
are willing to sign and extend the contracts.
All the same pricing except for ProTree is going to give us a 3% increase, which was available for them to do so.
And it's still considerably lower than the one that we had last time.
I mean, even with them going with the increase, it's still a real good deal.
But all of these companies, both in both electric, H and K electric for the as needed electric electrician service.
We only had one that renewed for asphalt paving services, which is teeter spaving.
On the open trench and boring, we had brought head boring,
B-town construction, Collins construction, and let's see here.
I think I need to help.
Thank you, Guillermo.
I brought that board.
My hands are dry.
So let's see here, M&J equipment.
And then ProTree is the one that does our high voltage line clearance and tree trimming and everything.
So we need to...
major approval to so we can get all of the amendments signed in everything.
Motion to approve.
Thank you.
Hi.
17 other new business.
If any of which is resistance,
supposing this agenda,
18 staff reports,
18 trustees, meeting announcements,
and 20, this meeting will be continued.
Council chambers,
and the staff reports,
and the executive session,
set the completion of these special meetings
at the final met,
and best of all public facilities.